# Abdulkabeer Akinlabi Habeebullah

habeebkabeer@gmail.com 08093921440 22 Adijatu Street, Ipaja Lagos Ipaja, Lagos

### Summary

Self-assured individual offering more than [10] years of experience as a Programmer. Highly trained in various technology environments. Flexible and poised promoting well-developed skills in software development and Web designing

Motivated Programmer with exceptional background spent in [coding] industry. Engaging demeanor known for working well in deadline-driven environments. Expert in front-end and backend technology.

Self-directed and motivated Software Engineer experienced working effectively in dynamic environments. Fluent in English, Arabic, Yoruba and Hausa and programming languages, including PHP, SQL, Javascript etc.

## **Experience**

## **YWC Technologies Limited**

Programmer • Abuja, FCT

02/2012 - 03/2014

- Developed software applications for clients which comprises of legal and law and educationapplications
- Contributed to [ASP.NET/SQL SERVER] based projects for automated deployment of software for some legal firms in Abuja (Law Office Management System.
- Debugged and modified software components.
- Designed and developed [2] computer software web applications:
   School Management System and E-Library

# **Dotnet Technologies Limited**

Programmer • Ikeja, Lagos

04/2015 - 05/2016

**Developing Software for clients** 

## **Mimbar Schools**

Chief ICt Officer • Ibadan, Oyo

04/2016 - 11/2019

Designed and manage the school website

Manage and Developed the school portal

Developed the school report system

## Ibn Qayyim Institute of Arabic and Programming

Programmer and Trainer • Ibadan, Oyo

01/2020 - Present

Training students in programming

### Skills

Bootsrap]; Angular JS
• Advanced knowledge of PHP and its
• Object Oriented Programming expertise

Advanced knowledge of PHP and its frameworks (CodeIgniter)

Ability to use MVC architecture in development

**Education** 

University of Ibadan

Islamic Studies • Ibadan, Oyo 07/2012

Second Class Upper Division

University of Ibadan

Islamic Studies • Ibadan, Oyo 04/2016

PhD Grade

University of Ibadan

Islamic Studies • Iadan, Oyo 03/2019

The Polytechnic Ile Ife

Computer Science • Ile Ife, Osun 08/2008

Languages

• Arabic • English

• Yoruba • Hausa